Guide to the South Asian Pamphlets Collection, 1920-2005 (bulk 1950-2000) RL.01235
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- India Pamphlets, 1920-2005, bulk 1960-1990, 177 boxes
  - International Relations, 1956-2003, 5 boxes
    - Declaration on South Asian Regional Cooperation and Joint Communique. South Asian Regional Cooperation Meeting of Foreign Ministers. New Delhi, Ministry of External Affairs, India: 1983. (Box IN-92)
    - Disarmament. All India Congress Committee (I), New Delhi. New Delhi, India: 198-? (Box IN-92)
    - Documents of the Eighth Congress of the Communist Party of Philippines (Partido Komunista Ng Pilipinas), December 1980. Communist Party of India, New Delhi. New Delhi, India: 1980. (Box IN-92)
    - Dynamics of the World Political Situation - A Revolutionary Marxist Perspective. Desai, A. R. Bombay, C.G. Shah Memorial Trust Publication, India: 1986. (Box IN-92)
      Report of the Twelfth World Congress of the Fourth International, 1985.
    - East German Propaganda Offensives and India. Patel, Dahyabhai V. New Delhi, FNFS, India: 1969. (Box IN-93)
    - Efforts for Peace. Ao, N. Bengang.Nagaland, Director of Information and Publicity, India: 196-? (Box IN-93)
    - Fight Back Against the Detractors of Non-Alignment. Mukherjee, Sadhan. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1983. (Box IN-93)
    - Final Communique of the Asian-American Conference. Bandung, Asian-African Conference, India: 1965. (Box IN-93)
      Held at Bandung from 18th-24th April, 1955.
    - For Peace and Progress. Gandhi, Indira. Delhi, Ministry of Information and Broadcasting, India: 1966. (Box IN-93)
    - Foreign Collaboration. India. Ministry of I. and B. Madras, India: 1964. (Box IN-93)
    - Foreign Funding & the Philosophy of Voluntary Organisations. Karat, Prakash. New Delhi, National Book Centre, India: 1988. (Box IN-93)
    - Foreign Minister in America, The. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1969. (Box IN-93)
    - Foreign Policy of the Indian National Congress, The. All India Congress Committee (I), New Delhi. New Delhi, India: [1983?] (Box IN-93)
      Edited and published by Chandulal Chandrakar M.P. Gen. Secretary, AICC (I), New Delhi.
    - Foreign Relations. Kaul, T. N. New Delhi, Publications Division, India: 1972. (Box IN-93)
    - Foundations of Peace. India. Ministry of Information & Broadcasting. New Delhi, Directorate of Advertising and Visual Publicity, India: 1968. (Box IN-93)
    - Fresh Look at Free China Policy Is Absolutely Essential, A. Tyabji, Badr-Ud-Din. Sawrup, Rama, Committee against the admission of Communist China to the United Nations, India: 196-? (Box IN-93)
    - From Wall to Wall. Patel, Dahyabhai V. Bombay, Society for Parliamentary Studies, India: 197-? (Box IN-93)
    - Future of Pakistan. Madhok, Balraj. New Delhi, Bharati Sahitya Sadan, India: 1971. (Box IN-93)
    - Glimpses of Revolutionary Cuba. Sharma, Yogindra. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1972. (Box IN-93)
    - Handclasps of Friendship France-India. Handclasps of Friendship. New Delhi, Malik, Satya Vir, India: 1963. (Box IN-93)
    - Handclasps of Friendship UAR-India. Handclasps of Friendship. New Delhi, Malik, Satya Vir, India: 1963. (Box IN-93)
    - Handclasps of Friendship USSR-India. Handclasps of Friendship. New Delhi, Malik, Satya Vir, India: 1963. (Box IN-93)
    - Handclasps of Friendship Yugoslavia- India. Handclasps of Friendship. New Delhi, Malik, Satya Vir, India: 1963. (Box IN-93)
    - Handclasps of Friendship: USA - India. Malik, Satya Vir. Delhi, [no publisher], India: 1963. (Box IN-93)
    - History of Moscow's Colonial Conquests, A. Sabharwal, Rama Swarup. New Delhi, APACL Literature, India: 1962. (Box IN-93)
    - Human Approach to World Peace, A. Lama, Dalai XIV. New Delhi, Narthang Publications, India: 1984. (Box IN-93)
    - Human Survival & Nuclear Disarmament. Rao, Chandrasekhara R. V. R. Hyderabad, Committee of One Hundred of Bertrand Russell Society, India: 1981. (Box IN-93)
      Fourth Bertrand Russel Memorial Lecture.
    - In Support of the Theory of the Differentiation of the Three Worlds. Hyderabad, The Proletariat Line Publications, India: 1979? (Box IN-94)
      Document reproduced from the Inaugural Issue of "The Proletarian Line".
    - Independence, Development, Disarmament and Peace Are Indivisible. Gandhi, Indira. New Delhi, Ministry of Information & Broadcasting, Govt. of India, India: 1983. (Box IN-94)
      Prime Minister Speaks-68.
    - India and China - A Brief Survey. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1966. (Box IN-94)
    - India and CPSU Congresses. Communist Party of India, New Delhi. New Delhi, India: 1981. (Box IN-94)
    - India and the Atom. India. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. New Delhi, India: 1981. (Box IN-94)
    - India and the Commonwealth: An Exhibition of Original Documents and Photographs. National Archives of India. New Delhi, India: 1983. (Box IN-94)
    - India and International Cooperation. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Delhi, India: 1961. (Box IN-94)
    - India and the International Scene. A.I.C.C.(I), New Delhi. New Delhi, India: 197-? (Box IN-94)
    - India and the United Nations. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1985. (Box IN-94)
    - India-China: Parliamentarians Exchange Visit. Indian Association of Parliamentarians on Population and Development. New Delhi, [no publisher], India: 1986. (Box IN-94)
    - India in the United Nations. India. Ministry of I. and B. New Delhi, India: 1964. (Box IN-94)
    - India-China Border Problem. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1962. (Box IN-94)
    - India's Role in South East Asia. Goray, N. G. Lucknow, Netaji Subhas Institute for Social Studies, India: 196-? (Box IN-94)
      Netaji Subhas Institute's Publication.
    - Indo-Nepal Treaty of Trade and Transit, 1971. India. Ministry of Foreign Trade. New Delhi, India: 1971. (Box IN-94)
    - Indo-Soviet Relations. Kapur, Harish, and Masani, M. R., and Gorwala, A. D. Bombay, Popular Prakashan, India: 196-? (Box IN-94)
    - Int'l Geographical Union: 12th General Assembly and 21st Int'l Geographical Congress Int'l Cartographic Association. Int'l Geographical Congress. Delhi, [no publisher], India: 1968. (Box IN-94)
    - Issue Brief - India and Nuclear Weapons - Updated 9/12/86. Martel, Mark, and Donnelly, Warren. Congressional Research Service, USA: 1986. (Box IN-94)
      Order Code IB86125.
    - Lenin and India. Sehanavis, Chinmohan. Calcutta, Gupta, Tarun Sen, India: 1969. (Box IN-94)
      Published on the occasion of Lenin's Birth Centenary.
    - Lessons of the Bengal Crisis. What Next? Masani, M. R., and Dandeker, N. Calcutta, India: 1968. (Box IN-94)
    - Let Pakistan Speak for Herself. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. New Delhi, India: 1971. (Box IN-94)
    - List Showing the Consular Corps, Deputy High Commissions and Trade Representations in India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, Govt. of India Press, India: 1975. (Box IN-94)
      January 1975.
    - Madame Binh - The Unwelcome Visitor. Patel, Dahyabhai V. Delhi, Society for Parliamentary Studies, India: 1970. (Box IN-94)
    - Middle East Crisis, The. Rao, B. Ramachandra. New Delhi, Kalamkar Prakashan Private Ltd., India: 1980. (Box IN-94)
    - Must India Go the Vietnam Way? Masani, M. R. New Delhi, Swatantra Party, India: 1967. (Box IN-94)
      Text of the speech delivered by Mr. M.R. Masani, M.P. at Sapru House, New Delhi on 27th July, 1967.
    - Namibian Question, The. India. Lok Sabha Secretariat. New Delhi, Lok Sabha Secretariat, India: 1988. (Box IN-94)
    - New Delhi Lauds India's Role. DAVP. New Delhi, India: 1983. (Box IN-94)
    - Non-Aligned Issues: A Perspective. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1981. (Box IN-94)
    - Non Aligned Movement. India. Lok Sabha Secretariat. New Delhi, India: 1986. (Box IN-94)
    - Non-Aligned Summit - An Assessment. Surjeet, H. S. New Delhi, National Book Centre, India: 1983. (Box IN-94)
      Reflects an assessment by the Communist Party of India (Marxist).
    - Non-Alignment: A Blueprint for Peace. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: [1982]. (Box IN-94)
    - Non-Alignment and Beyond. Soedjatmoko. New Delhi, Training Division, Dept. of Personnel and Administrative Reforms, India: 1983. (Box IN-94)
      Includes concluding remarks by Indira Gandhi.
    - Non-Alignment Today. Rao, P. V. Narasimha. New Delhi, Ministry of External Affairs, India: 1981? (Box IN-94)
    - North Vietnam's Campaign Against India. Swarup, Rama. New Delhi, Friends of Republic of Vietnam Society, India: 196-? (Box IN-94)
    - Nuclear Policy for India. Swamy, S. [Delhi], Bharatiya Jana Sangh, India: 1968. (Box IN-94)
    - On Marshal Ye Jianying's National Day Speech, On the Decision of the Plenary Session of the C.C., C.P.C. Basavapunnaiah, M. New Delhi, Communist Party of India (Marxist), India: 1980. (Box IN-94)
    - On Recent Developments in South East-Asia: An Appeal to the Communists All Over the World. Socialist Unity Centre of India, Calcutta. Calcutta, India: 1979. (Box IN-94)
    - On the Wings of Friendship. India. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Calcutta, Directorate of Advertising and Visual Publicity, India: 1969? (Box IN-94)
    - Open Letter of the Central Committee of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union to Party Organisations and All Communists in the Soviet Union. Communist Party of India, New Delhi. New Delhi, India: 1963. (Box IN-94)
    - Other Side of Indo-Sri Lanka Agreement. Veeramani, K. Madras, Dravidar Kazhagam, India: 1987. (Box IN-94)
    - Pacific Pact: Peace or War ? Communist Party of India, New Delhi. New Delhi, India:196-? (Box IN-94)
    - Pakistan War Postures. All India Congress Committee (I). New Delhi, AICC (I), India: 1983? (Box IN-94)
    - Palestine - The Indian Viewpoint. Faleiro, Eduardo. New Delhi, India Press Agency, India: 1985. (Box IN-94)
    - Panama Canal Dispute. Parihar, R. R. Jullundur, Rama Krishna and Sons, India: 196-? (Box IN-94)
    - Paris Agreement - Its Aftermath. Jain, A. P. New Delhi, [no publisher], India: 197-? (Box IN-94)
    - Peace and Friendship. India. Ministry of I. and B. New Delhi, India: 1976. (Box IN-94)
    - Perestroika for India. Aiyar, Swaminathan S. Anklesaria. Bombay, Forum of Free Enterprise, India: 1990. (Box IN-94)
    - PLO-Lebanese Fight Back: Israel's Proxy War for USA. Mukherjee, Sadhan. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1982. (Box IN-94)
    - Political Renaissance in Africa. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 196-? (Box IN-95)
    - President Leonid Brezhnev Visits India. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1980. (Box IN-95)
    - Prime Minister Indira Gandhi at the Seventh Non-Aligned Summit. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1983? (Box IN-95)
      The New Delhi Message.
    - Prime Minister Rajiv Gandhi Visits Egypt. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1985. (Box IN-95)
    - Prime Minister Rajiv Gandhi Visits France. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1985. (Box IN-95)
    - Problems of Marxism and World Politics: Debate Between Communist Parties of Italy and the Soviet Union. Calcutta, Pearl Publishers, India: 1982. (Box IN-95)
      A Collection of Documents of the ICP and CPSU.
    - Quit Commonwealth. Gupta, Bhupesh. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1965. (Box IN-95)
    - Red China and the United Nations. Cominick, Peter H. New Delhi, Asian Peoples' Anti-Communist League, India: 196-? (Box IN-95)
    - Report of the Follow-up Seminar on ICA Fellowship Programme. Int'l Cooperative Alliance. New Delhi, [no publisher], India: 1968. (Box IN-95)
    - Report of the Fourth Congress of the People's Revolutionary Party of Kampuchea. Communist Party of India, New Delhi. New Delhi, India: 1981. (Box IN-95)
    - Revolution of the 17th of June 1953. Patel, Dahyabhai V. New Delhi, Asian Peoples' Anti-Communist League, India: 1965. (Box IN-95)
    - Rights of 75 Million People of Bangladesh to Life, Liberty and Pursuit of Happiness. Gandhi, Indira. New Delhi, [no publisher], India: 1971. (Box IN-95)
      Letter from Shrimati Indira Gandhi, to His Excellency Mr. Richard Nixon.
    - Role of Stalin as the CPI(M) Views It. New Delhi, National Book Centre, India: 1987. (Box IN-95)
      A Collection of Documents.
    - SAARC Nations Should Stand Together to Fight Poverty. Shekhar, Chandra. New Delhi, Ministry of Information and Broadcasting, India: 1990. (Box IN-95)
    - Second SAARC Summit Bangalore India. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1986. (Box IN-95)
    - Self-Reliance in Defence. All India Congress Committee, New Delhi. New Delhi, India: 197-? (Box IN-95)
    - Simla Agreement - Debates in Lob Sabha/Rajya Sabha. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1972. (Box IN-95)
      Replies by the Prime Minister and the Minister of External Affairs.
    - Sino-Indian Relations. Chakravarti, P. C. Calcutta, Javadpur University, India: 1959. (Box IN-95)
      Jadavpur University Extension Lecture.
    - Sino-Soviet Conflict? Swamy, K. N. Vijayawada, Swamy Publications, India: 1961. (Box IN-95)
    - Situation and Further Tasks in Czechoslovakia. Husak, Gustav. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1969. (Box IN-95)
    - Six-Nation Summit on Nuclear Disarmament- New Delhi: January 28, 1985. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1985. (Box IN-95)
    - Socialist German State: Inspiring Impressions. Rao, C. Rajeshwara. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1972. (Box IN-95)
    - Southern Asia-Pacific Current Trends. Faleiro, Eduardo., and Rasgota, Maharajakrishna, and Misra, K. P. New Delhi, Int'l Institute for Southers Asia-Pacific Studies, India: 1987. (Box IN-95)
    - Soviet New Thinking and Policies. Sardesai, S. G., and Reddy, N. Rajasekhara, and Parakal, Pauly V. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1988. (Box IN-95)
    - Statements by Mrs. Indira Gandhi Prime Minister of India in Parliament on Sri Lanka Situation. Gandhi, Indira. New Delhi, Ministry of External Affairs, India: 1983 August. (Box IN-96)
    - Status of Tibet in International Law, The. Anand, R. P. New Delhi, School of Int'l Studies, India: 1969. (Box IN-96)
      This paper was originally published in International Studies, Vol 10, No. 4, April 1969.
    - Stop Reagan: Save World from Nuclear Holocaust. Parakal, Pauly V. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1982. (Box IN-96)
    - Struggle in Mozambique- A Firsthand Report. Johansson, Anders. New Delhi, Indian Council for Africa, India: 196-? (Box IN-96)
    - Survey of the World's Communist Parties, A. New Delhi, Free News and Feature Services, India: 1970. (Box IN-96)
    - Tashkent Declaration. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1966. (Box IN-96)
    - Tashkent Declaration: 7 Questions Answered. India. Ministry of I. & B. New Delhi, India: 1966. (Box IN-96)
    - Tashkent Spirit, The. Chandra, Romesh. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1966. (Box IN-96)
      India's Banner for Today.
    - Tashkent, An Episode or An Epitome? Menon, K. P. S. Madras, National Book Club Publication, India: 1966. (Box IN-96)
    - Telegraph Conspiracy, The. "Campaign Against Abuse of Media Power". Calcutta, [no publisher], India: 1987. (Box IN-96)
      A case study of yellow Journalism at its worst.
    - Three Decades of Indian Republic: India's Initiatives in Foreign Policy. Rao, P. V. Narasimha. New Delhi, Ministry of External Affairs, Govt. of India, India: 1981. (Box IN-96)
    - To Whom Does the Sinai Belong? A No-Man's Land. New Delhi, Society for Parliamentary Studies, India: 1969. (Box IN-96)
    - Treaty of Friendship, Cooperation and Peace between the Republic of India and the People's Republic of Bangladesh, The. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1972. (Box IN-96)
      Signed at Dacca on March 19, 1972.
    - Treaty of Peace, Friendship and Cooperation between the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics and the Republic of India, The. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1971. (Box IN-96)
    - Truth about the Peace Corps. [An Observer]. New Delhi, People's Publishing House, India: 1968. (Box IN-96)
    - Twentieth Russian Congress and Indian Communists. Lohia, Rammanohar. [New Delhi], India: 1956. (Box IN-96)
      A Socialist Critique.
    - U. N. Assembly Session. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1967. (Box IN-96)
      Sardar Swaran Singh's Address.
    - UNESCO in Twenty-Five Years: A Retrospect and Prospect. Adiseshiah, Malcolm S. New Delhi, National Council of Educational Research and Training, India: 1971. (Box IN-96)
      UNESCO Silver Jubilee.
    - U.S. Big Stick Policy - Seventh Fleet in Indian Ocean. Natarajan, L. New Delhi, Perspective Publications, India: 196-? (Box IN-96)
    - United States, India, and South Asia: Interests, Trends, and Issues for Congressional Concern, The. Subcommittee on Asian & Pacific Affairs.Committee on International Relations. Washington, [no publisher], USA: 1978. (Box IN-96)
      Prepared at the request of the Subcommittee on Asian and Pacific Affairs by the Congressional Research Service Library of Congress.
    - Universal Peace Conference 1983 - Souvenir. Madras, Govt. of India, India: 1983. (Box IN-96)
    - Universal Peace Conference. Brahma Kumaris World Spiritual University. Rajasthan, [no publisher], India: 1983. (Box IN-96)
      Universal Peace Charter: for peace in international relations, professional relations and inter-personal relations, and peace of mind.
    - Untruths Exposed: India-West Asia Tangle. "A student of West Asian Affairs". New Delhi, Society for Parliamentary Studies, India: 197-? (Box IN-96)
    - Viet Cong Terrorism Against Revolutionary Programme in South Vietnam. Swarup, Rama. New Delhi, Asian Peoples' Anti-Communist League, India: 196-? (Box IN-96)
    - Vietnam - Twenty Years of Unity, Struggle and Victory. Dong, Pham Van. New Delhi, Consulate General of the D. R. V. in India, India: 1965. (Box IN-96)
      Consulate General of the D.R.V. in India.
    - Visit to Nationalist China, A. Masani, M. R., and Swarup, Rama. New Delhi, Asian Peoples' Anti-Communist League, India Chapter, India: 1962. (Box IN-96)
      APACL Literature, New Delhi.
    - Vital International Issues: Palestine, Namibia, Grenada, Central America, Cyprus. A.I.C.C.(I), New Delhi. New Delhi, India: 1983. (Box IN-96)
    - Voting on China Representation Issue in the United States - An Analysis. New Delhi, Committee Against the Admission of Communist China to the United Nations, India: 196-? (Box IN-96)
    - Wanted: A National Foreign Policy. Sondhi, M. L. [Delhi], Bharatiya Jana Sangh, India: 1968. (Box IN-96)
    - War or Peace? Jain, A. P. New Delhi, [no publisher], India: 1972. (Box IN-96)
      Current Initiatives in Vietnam.
    - Welfare Economics and Growing Inequalities in South Asia. Shukla, A. C. Kanpur, [no publisher], India: 2003. (Box IN-96)
      ACDIS Occasional Paper.
    - What Do They Want to Achieve by this 'Cultural Revolution' in China. Adhikari, G. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1966. (Box IN-96)
    - What Peking Keeps Silent About: What Mao Said Before but Contradicts Today. New Delhi, People's Publishing House, India: 1972. (Box IN-96)
    - Who Needs the Arab League?"A Student of West Asian Affairs". New Delhi, Society for Parliamentary Studies, India: 1969. (Box IN-96)
      A Reply to its Memorandum of November 6, 1969.
    - Why Not Diplomatic Relations with Israel?"A Student of West Asian Affairs". New Delhi, Society for Parliamentary Studies, India: 197-? (Box IN-96)
    - Will China Invade India? Swamy, K. N. Vijayawada, Swamy Publications, India: 1961. (Box IN-96)
    - Will Red China Risk a World War? Swamy, K. N. Vijayawada, Swamy Publications, India: 196-? (Box IN-96)
    - World Communist Movement: 1847-1876. Rajimwale, Anil. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1974. (Box IN-96)
    - World Communist Movement: 1876-1914. Rajimwale, Anil. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1975. (Box IN-96)
    - World Crisis: How to Serve the Interests of the South? Tinbergen, Jan. New Delhi, Research and Information System for the Non-Aligned and other Developing Countries, India: 1984. (Box IN-96)
      RIS Occasional Paper III.
    - World Says 'No' to Nuclear War. Communist Party of India, New Delhi. New Delhi, India: 1984. (Box IN-96)
    - World Significance of the Founding of USSR. Communist Party of India, New Delhi. New Delhi, India: 1973. (Box IN-96)
    - Year After: Indo-Sri Lanka Agreement, A. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 198-? (Box IN-96)
    - Yugoslavia: Problems and Perspectives. Dange, S. A. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1973. (Box IN-96)
  - Kashmir Question, 1959-2005, 2 boxes
    The 36 pamphlets in this section were published by official government agencies and NGOs. Some pamphlets articulate arguments by Indian nationalists, mostly Hindus, making a case for Kashmir to stay in India. Other topics include the historical background on Pakistani aggression in Kashmir, the viewpoints of various political parties, the issue of autonomy, and the policies of the Government of Jammu and Kashmir. Some maps of areas in question are also found here.
    - Aggression in Kashmir. India. Ministry of External Affairs. Delhi, Publications Division, India: 1963. (Box IN-97)
    - Basis for a Dialogue on Kashmir. Puri, Balraj. Jammu, Samajwadi Bhawan, India: 1969. (Box IN-97)
    - Challenge in Kashmir, The. All India Congress Committee (I), New Delhi. New Delhi, India: 198-? (Box IN-97)
    - Change in Kashmir in National Interest. Ahmed, Tasnim. New Delhi, AICC(I) Publication Dept., India: 198-? (Box IN-97)
    - Crisis in Perspective, The. India. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. New Delhi, India: 1965. (Box IN-97)
    - Defence Democracy Secularism: Kashmir. Sardesai, S. G. New Delhi, Communist Party Publication, India: 1965. (Box IN-97)
    - Great Task Ahead Part II. Jammu and Kashmir. Dept. of Information. Srinagar, India: 1965. (Box IN-97)
      (Text of the speech made by the P.M. Shri G.M. Sadiq in reply to the debate on the Sadar-i-Riyasat's Address to the J&K Legislative Council).
    - Great Tasks Ahead. Jammu and Kashmir. Dept. of Information. Srinagar, India: 1965. (Box IN-97)
      (Text of the speech made by the P.M. Shri G.M. Sadiq in reply to the debate on the Sadar-i-Riyasat's Address to the J&K Legislative Assembly).
    - India Defends Democracy. Srinagar, Educational Publishers, India: 1965. (Box IN-97)
    - Indian and Pakistan Converging Interests for Peace. Kumar, Dinesh. Jerusalem, Jerusalem Institute for Western Defence, Israel: 2005. (Box IN-97)
      Bulletin of the Jerusalem Institute for Western Defence. (Volume 18, Bulletin 2).
    - Jammu Demands Justice. Bhartiya Janata Party, Jammu and Kashmir State. Jammu, Bhartiya Janata Party, India: 198-? (Box IN-97)
      Memorandum to the President of India (Camp Jammu), the Speaker (Legislative assembly of J&K), a note on Jammu's Share in the Delimitation of Assembly seats.
    - Jammu's Discontent: Causes and Cures. Puri, Balraj. New Delhi, Jammu and Kashmir Commission of Enquiry, India: 1968. (Box IN-97)
      Memorandum submitted to the Gajendragadkar Commission (Jammu Autonomy Forum).
    - Kashmir - At a Glance. Jammu and Kashmir. Dept. of Information. Srinagar, India: 1961. (Box IN-97)
    - Kashmir Accord, The. Gandhi, Indira. New Delhi, [no publisher], India: 1975. (Box IN-97)
      Statement of Smt. Indira Gandhi, Prime Minister, in Parliament on J&K on February 24, 1975.